It's your fault.
Because you can't get
to the last word, I have
to stand under these
whole spotlights for so long.
Boah!
Phew, it's so hot.
Now I have to take
something off again. Man.
Wobble!
So, the animal lives in Africa and
these letters appear in its name.
An Ö and an E.
In Africa. Shit, that's hard.
One very last tip: The
animal lives in the desert.
I've got it, I've
got it. Desert dog.
Potato head. Desert dog.
Doesn't it have four letters?
The last ten
seconds are running.
- Crap.
- Ten, nine, eight...
- Wait, wait, wait!
- ...seven, six...
- Ö and E. Kö..., Rö...
- ...an animal in the desert.
- Dö...
- Three, two, one.
Seagull!
Too late, unfortunately!
- No.
- Oh man, ey.
- We knew it, we knew it.
- Ey, that doesn't count.
Should I ask the production
if we can get a little extension?
- Si, si.
- Please.
Ah, I see now.
It worked.
Si!
So, if
someone figured it out,
they can still call in
during our Special Bonus Time.
Quick, spaghetti,
quick, quick, quick!
Oh, I can't take it anymore.
By the time I give away the cash prize,
I'll probably be wearing nothing at all.
Super, ey, everything naked, ey. Package
full of money and everything naked, ey.
Ey, totally naked!
Incredlbile, the television
become always better.
Hello, you are at Tele
11, your winnings channel.
- Si.
- Many thanks for calling.
Naturally, because I know
now, the animals is a seagull.
- Exactly!
- Unfortunately, all lines are currently busy.
Yes!
Ah, send the money to
Mario Bartolo in Köln-Kalk.
Yes, and to Tommie Krause, right.
We look forward to
your next call.
Yes, we too. Bye!
Tommie, we gotta celebrate this.
Ey, but totally! Yeah!
This is insane! Why are
you sending me to hell?
Hell, hell, hell, hell.
Hey, Bruno, give me another one, come on!
Another round!
Ey, Spaghetti,
today you lose.
No, potato head,
you're gonna fold!
- I ain't!
- You sure are!
- I'm definitely not.
- Andiamo!
Hey boys.
Don't you have to go to work?
Work.
Every morning the same shit.
Shit job.
Shit!
Mario, I'm too drunk, ey.
I can't walk no more.
Luckily, we have the car.
Driving always works.
Right there.
Get in the bucket. Si.
Prego!
Tommie, where do we have
the patrol today actually?
No idea.
Wait, wait, stop for a sec.
I gotta pee.
Ey!
Who's throwing wheels
around here? What's that about?
Gotta go left!
Mario.
Back.
Watch out!
Aren't those the colleagues
Bartolo and Krause?
Bartolo and Krause. Colleagues?
I've missed that, Colleague Beveler.
Ey, Mario. Here!
Si! Here we do
the surveillance.
But first
a little nap.
Bene.
Sick, ey. Officer.
Someone's tired here.
Hello! You've gotta have
your people under control.
Ey, Mario!
Action!
No, they're not
doing that with us.
Si.
Negative. Just listen to me!
Moment!
Wait a minute. Yes?
Didn't you see?
It's red.
Yeah, okay.
No, no, no, no. That's not
okay! Because that's forbidden.
Aha.
You have broken the laws.
I broke the law?
Si.
Broke it.
I broke the law. And what
is my punishment now?
We wanting today
not be so strict.
It was only a
verbal warning.
Oh, no. Please not that one.
The rat.
Shit, man!
Well, sometimes I
do wonder...
Go ahead and say it.
How some scum like that
was taken into the police force.
I'd actually
like to know that too.
Police...
...headquarters.
Tommie! He's here.
Good morning.
Look over there.
Ma che bella signorina.
What do you want?
What we wanting?
What we want?
You want to speak to
the Police Commissioner?
Yes, we want to offer
him something like this.
What do you want
to offer him then?
Yes, us.
Si. Our labor. Because we
both want become police.
Exactly. Like cops, yeah.
Totally cool cops, ey.
How do you
get that idea?
Yeah, because a cop, you
can't kick him out of any pub.
No. You can
keep partying.
And if the neighbors complain,
they get a warning immediately.
Ey, and the beer on the head, yeah.
Because last round is still
on, when the police say so.
That's why it's called
police hour.
So you want to become policemen to
go to the pub for as long as possible?
Si.
But not only. Also like going to
the stadium, watch some football.
Exactly. 'Cause as a cop,
you get right to the front.
Si. Fantastico. But Tommie,
what is the best of all.
Ey, the absolute best.
Ey, these are the... boah!
Ey, the police chicks!
What expectations do you
actually have of the police service?
No fear.
We know exactly how go.
Sure, sure.
We have seen all the movies.
Si.
Ey, ''Karate-Cop''
Part 1 to 7, yeah.
And then, ey,
''Cop-chicks bang hard''.
Ey, greedy, ey!
And and and and ''RoboCop'', ey.
Si. RoboCope.
He always go like that.
He, he!
Now that's enough!
Drrr, drrr. I have shot you
in the name of the laws.
Ey, wait, wait, Mario.
Watch out!
I'll be the Karate Cop now
and you're the Master of Doom.
Va bene. I attack you
with the tiger claw.
No chance!
Did you see that, ey?
Ey, tiger claw knife-hand block.
The guy is totally powerless.
Hey, Tommie.
I got you.
Ey, Spaghetti, you'll pay for that!
You'll pay for that!
Come on, come on, Tommie!
My flowers!
Come on! Come,
come, come. Haha!
You can't catch me!
Tommie! Ow, no! Tommie!
Stop it! Right now!
Stand up!
Your identification, please.
Tommie Krause, Kalker
Weg 34 in Cologne-Kalk.
Mario Bartolo. Same address.
When can we
finally start now?
Si. When do we get
our employment?
You won't be getting hired. You'll be
getting a charge for property damage.
And one thing I can assure you. You
two will never become police officers.
Guys, guys, guys! Wait.
Hey, how did we play?
The FC was really good, although the
Schalke guys were smashing it like crazy.
Good, Hennes, Hennes, Hennes!
This goat is the best
talisman in the whole world.
Yeah, normal!
Then Podolski scored a banger
for us. Like, boom! A real thumper.
Si.
But the ref disallowed it and
then the others got a penalty.
In the end, it was zero to one.
- Ah!
- No.
Lost. What a joke.
S zero four! League leaders, league leaders!
We wanna see that again.
Wait!
Yo, that's gonna be a huge report.
What's up?
Disturbing the peace. That's what's up!
Si. And gathering in packs.
Hey, hold on.
What? Hold on. Yo
Mario. Did you hear that?
Si. Resisting authority.
Costs 500 Euros.
But for each person.
Five hundred?
How are we
supposed to pay for that?
Is your problem.
I think I'm totally screwed. Man,
we just want to celebrate something!
Okay.
You can make it up.
Yeah. And how?
Stand at attention!
And go.
1. FC Köln is the best
team in all of Germany.
Hennes, the buck, is beautiful.
More beautiful than us.
Our goal was sneaky.
We are ashamed of it.
We want that in reality
the 1. FC Köln...
FC! FC! FC! FC!
Ey, right!
FC! FC! FC!
Good. And now kiss the flag!
That one there!
Stop!
On the asses of the goats.
No, I can't do that.
Immediately!
Va bene!
Well done.
Now you can go.
We'll see each other
again at Schalke.
Ey, there, there, there!
There, there, there, there! Ey, greedy!
Ey come on. One glass.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Stop,
stop, stop. Stop. Stop!
What is going on here? Why are
you jumping in front of my car?
Food inspection.
What?
Come on! Pour a few Kölsches.
- Yes, let's go!
- Huh!
Yeah, nothing, nothing, nothing.
Not the small ones, the big ones, ey.
I want beer. More beer.
Alright.
- Cheers!
- Post-thirst is the best thirst.
- Ah, exactly!
Ey, come here.
Accident inspection.
Ey, what do we do
now with this shit here?
Ah, let's take the license plates off
and send the cars to the scrapyard.
Ey, exactly, ey. Gone is gone!
Willi's here.
Ah, Mario.
Good evening, dear colleagues.
Ah, you're here too?
Yes.
The boss wants to speak with you.
Indeed. He said it was urgent.
Markus.
Yes, Mr. Bartolo?
You... surely you haven't...
What?
Told the boss anything?
No, I didn't tell him
anything. Not a word.
You're a good man, Markus.
I wrote it to him.
Well, gentlemen.
Two disciplinary violations
you both already have.
And today there was
another incident.
There we caught a
perpetrator.
He was totally against the law.
And then you felt so sick, that
you spontaneously had to throw up.
Vomited over the poor
man.
Fully covered him from top to
bottom-, totally fouled him up.
That was only for a very short time.
Tommie only spat a
tiny bit.
Exactly. And then he
looked at me quite cheekily.
Si. He probably wanted to say
something like insulting an officer.
100%. I saw it exactly.
Strange. Really very strange.
Mr. Bartolo, Mr. Krause.
I'm transferring you with
immediate effect to the bicycle squad.
Your new area of operation will
be the street in front of our station.
So that I always
have you in sight.
So, that's it, gentlemen.
You can go now.
Ma... Chef e.
Get out of here!
Enjoy your dinner.
What a disgrace!
They took our
beautiful car away.
Si. Why they do that?
And the pistol.
Totally unfair, ey. Man!
So we should drive?
He's to blame for everything.
The pig, the pig. The super-pig.
Ey, Mario. We gotta
get him in the ass.
Si.
It's best if we set
a Doberman on him.
Ey, wait, wait, wait. It
has to be even worse.
Si, much worse.
Ey, much, much worse.
Si. Tommie, I have an idea.
Mario, some beast, that
really goes wild, yeah.
That bites like hell, yeah.
Tommie, predator enclosure.
There, there, there, there,
there. That one would be super.
That one would be super, but I
think it's a bit too big for our cages.
Too bad.
Bye, Pussycat.
Just rabbits and goats, ey.
Such a stupid camel.
That's no use.
Ey, wait, wait.
Tasmanian Devil.
The Tasmanian Devil is a
highly aggressive predator...
- Super, ey.
- ...with his razor-sharp teeth.
Ey, Mario. That's him, ey.
Va bene.
Tommie, he's wild.
Ey, let him be, let him be.
Ow.
Ey, watch out,
watch out, watch out.
- Ow, ow.
- Away, away.
Tommie! Ow, ow.
Perce dio.
Wow, he's really wired, ey.
Careful, careful,
careful. Watch out!
- Motore.
- He's in. Yes.
Good morning, dear Mr. Heinrich.
Yes. And have a
nice working day.
Mr. Wittmann, may I
be of assistance to you?
Yes, that would be nice.
Thank you, Mr. Heinrich.
Now they've already blocked
me in again. Good grief.
Well, this is truly an outrage.
I will immediately determine the
name of the person who parked illegally.
Mr. Wittmann, I
could drive you as well.
No.
Yes, that would be very helpful.
- I'm sorry?
- Hm?
- You...
- Nah.
Damn it all.
Maybe he's not
even biting today.
Arnold 1936, please come in.
Yes, Arnold 1936
here. What's going on?
Is colleague Markus
Heinrich near you guys?
Yes, but he's unavailable right now.
Who's gone?
Whoa. Nah, no panic. We'll
take care of it. Immediately.
- What?
- That can't be true!
Tommie, what's
happening? Did they kill one?
Worse, much worse. The billy
goat has been stolen from 1. FC Köln.
Hennes?
- Yes. Immediately, get over there fast!
- Yes.
Ey, Mario. That's sneaky! Ey,
totally sneaky. Ey, total sabotage.
Si. Without the goats, the
FC has no luck left, Tommie.
Man, ey. Man. Ey, of all times now, when the
important cup game is the day after tomorrow.
Against who we play?
- Against Munich.
- Madonna!
At the last game the Billy Goat was
still down there at the outer stand.
More I don't know also.
My boy, for the police
work we need witness.
Ey Mario. Look there, there, there!
Mamma mia.
The cheer-sluts.
Tommie, ma che belle ragazzi.
Ey, totally hot witnesses, ey.
Tommie, this is the
paradise in red and white.
Boah.
They have such beautiful pom-poms.
Insanity.
- Ouch! Watch out!
- Sorry.
That was Bartolo and
Krause. I'm quite sure of it.
Your interest in Bartolo and Krause
is starting to seem suspicious to me.
The two of them were sneaking
around my car this morning.
They did this creature intentionally
and with malicious intent...
Oh, poppycock. I don't
believe a word you say.
Excuse me?
Anyway. We will investigate
this case very, very thoroughly.
And as for Bartolo and
Krause, don't worry about them.
I'll take care of them.
If I may ask a
question, Mr. Wittmann.
What now?
How did the two of them
actually end up with us?
Well...
On...
...personal recommendation
of the police chief.
Oh, that...
...that is obviously
something else.
Oh, uhm. excuse me.
Si. We'll come back later.
Yes.
They're probably
here because of Hennes.
Ey, that they stole him,
is such a mean thing.
But really.
Now they are naked.
No, Tommie. No.
Aspetta, aspetta.
You must have patience. Patience.
Andiamo.
Scusi.
We have to do
a questioning now.
Who among you saw the
goat last?
Well, the last time I saw
him, he was in the enclosure.
Write it down.
Enclosure.
Alright. The goat, did he still
have the FC-scarf around him?
No.
So he was just standing
around without the scarf?
Tommie.
Signorina.
Wait.
So if anyone saw the goat last,
it must be the zookeeper.
What?
Yeah, sure. Addi.
Si, si, si. Addi. Si.
Addi, we know him well.
Where is he now?
I raised that little
goat like my own child.
It even slept in my little bed.
You want to tell us anything else?
Yeah.
Then say it...
How did it happen?
How did this mess
happen? How did it happen?
Crooks were in a hurry...
and just ran off like that?
Everyone in one direction?
And then they strangled the goat.
But the goat fought back.
Fought back hard, right.
And then he was dead.
Stone dead. Poor Hennes.
Uhm... Addi?
Get away from the bed! Away!
Wow, cool.
Luckily, he's alive.
Now just wait already.
Where are you guys going?
We gotta ask him something.
Listen, we gotta
ask him something.
- Allora.
- We are police!
You have no access here.
Wait a moment, I...
Hey, man, ey! Shit!
- Si!
- Hey, we'll never find Hennes like this.
He's gotta stop
drinking immediately.
- We have to...
- Would you possibly take care of that?
Oh. Capito.
Tommie.
Buon giorno.
Hey, Mario. Look there.
Addi, pay attention.
Oh man, ey, isn't it.
Tommie, watch out.
- Heaven sent you.
- What?
Listen. You call that
secured up there?
Yeah, yeah, I secured it.
I'm telling you, I'm sending you
to the shrink over there in a second.
So, you have
little Henry...
Henry the Second.
Never once in his life
let off the leash
because you have severe
fear of loss?
I feel so
sorry for him, but...
I, I just
can't do it.
And because you believe that
these men are returning to your life?
These two men
who kill all your pets?
- Mhm.
- Two men who stalk you and who always
and everywhere only cause terrible havoc.
Exactly.
Intestinal obstruction, third
stage. We must act immediately.
Si, si.
Yes, but first we have
to go to someone else.
Professor, we urgently need your
help. After all, you're the bowel pope.
Yes, yes, but...
But we still have to
go somewhere else first.
I'm begging you.
If you don't intervene, he'll
die within the next ten minutes.
So.
I've gotta go. We have another emergency
next door and then this one here, oh God.
What a day.
Mario, we have to go to Addi.
Si, Tommie. But we are
police. We must help.
Yes, police are supposed to help.
Hey.
Bowel obstruction.
It can't be
that hard, can it?
Si. It's best if we just
take everything out first.
Yes. Yes.
Damn, that's long, ey.
Si. It's just not stopping anymore.
Where is it now, then
this bowel obstruction, eh?
I don't know.
In that belly there, but
everything is all mixed up, eh. Man.
Super sound, Tommie.
Full blast, eh.
Tommie, Tommie,
play the organ.
Yeah, for sure.
Bella musica.
Ey, wait, wait, wait!
Now we're doing
a session, eh.
Va bene.
Wait, wait.
Listen, it's really pulling
quite a bit up there, right?
Yeah, that's the nature of the thing.
All right. Shall we take a break.
So, if these evil
men weren't here right now, there
would actually
be nothing against you putting Henry
the Second on the
floor and letting him off the leash.
Is that right?
Yes.
And? Are they here?
No.
So.
Ey, Mario. She's got
a super pump, right?
Yes.
Tommie, listen. There's even a
fur, if you tickle, it sounded good.
Ey, wait. I'll give
it more gas, yeah.
Ey!
Alright.
Ey, this has to be faster.
Go full throttle, Tommie!
Alright!
What in God's name is
going on here, please?
That was the bowel obstruction.
Indeed.
She's awake!
It's not that bad, is it?
Bad? She's been in a
coma for three years.
You... You are geniuses.
You are magicians.
Many thanks.
Addi, Addi, Addi,
Addi. Addi, tell me.
We need to talk to you.
Who stole the goat?
Munich?
Why Munich?
Wart on the butt.
- Hello?
- Buon giorno.
Come on, Tommie.
Hey, where are you taking him?
There.
You may let go of Henry II now.
Wait a moment. I, I'll
be ready in a second.
There are no dangerous men here.
Move it, potato-head!
Scusi!
Well, how do you feel now?
Suddenly very light.
Everything is lifting off me.
See. The threat only
existed in your head.
Ey, get outta here!
He's alive. Nothing happened.
So, Munich.
And some guy with
a wart on his ass.
Si, we'll get him.
The cup match against the Bayerns isn't
until the day after tomorrow here in Cologne.
If we find the goat in Munich, yeah,
and we bring it here to the stadium...
Ey, they'll freak out. Then we'll
be the super-cops of all Cologne.
Si.
Ey, boah, ey! What a machine!
Tommie, look.
Who's sitting in there.
Ey, that... that's...
That's Jupp.
Wait, wait, wait!
Ey, ey, ey, ey!
Moment!
Good day... Police!
Bicycle squad!
Ey, you still remember me?
From where?
You once gave us
a Cologne-Kalk ban.
Because I was supposed to bring
you a crate of Ramsdorfer Kölsch.
But I didn't do it.
Exactly seven o'clock. With 20
bottles of Ramsdorfer Kölsch.
Just one bottle too few, one
minute too late. Cologne-Kalk ban.
Get out! Now!
Ow!
Driver's license, please.
And the vehicle registration.
And the TÜV. And the ASU.
Please.
Tommie, look.
It's a really ugly picture.
Ey, totally ugly.
Just total crap.
Listen up, my friend.
Don't "please" me. You're
standing right over it.
Let me be. Was that it?
Yes.
Here, please.
Just kidding, just kidding.
Here.
Give me that thing, man.
No, please don't. Please, please!
You're on probation, aren't you.
Oh, oh, oh.
- Jupp, please, please.
- You got pretty lucky there.
Tommie, there's no fine
dust sticker here at all.
Oh, shit!
Sorry, then you can't drive
with this vehicle no more.
Car keys please.
Did you see, Tommie?
Did you see his face?
Boah, man, he was so pissed.
Ey, he's boiling, he's fuming.
Yeah, those shitty cops,
I'm gonna wreck them.
- My beautiful Camaro!
- Yep, yep, yep!
Ey, Mario! Ey, cop, this
is so freaking cool, man.
You can do whatever you want.
And with the Camaro we
are in Munich in no time.
And get Hennes back.
Munich.
What you think, Tommie?
Who kidnapped the goat?
Munich...
Yeah, normal. Ey, Bayern Munich.
Of course, Tommie.
The cup game.
They are scared of the FC, you see.
They want not to lose the cup game.
That Rummenigge there
and Hoeneß and Beckenbauer.
Ey, they're just jealous. 'Cause
they don't have a talisman, see.
Tommie...
Now I know.
On the Sportschau
Hoeneß said it himself:
"With that Franz,
you can steal horses."
- And whoever steals the horses...
- He'll steal a billy goat too!
Madonna. This Beckenbauer I'd
never have thought that of him.
Ey, and someone like
that calls himself Kaiser.
Allora, travel provisions.
And travel beer.
Ey, Mario.
What do we actually do if
Beckenbauer
doesn't want to hand over the goat?
We'll use a police grip. Keep
going until he really snaps.
Normal. But, but what if
the guy gets reinforcements?
Ey, those Bavarians,
they're hard.
Si, Tommie. They'll be stuffing themselves
with such thick white sausages tomorrow.
And at lunch, they'll be shoving
down those pork knuckles.
Ey, those guys, they're big,
ey. And they're totally strong.
Tommie...
we need weapons!
Yeah...
weapons.
And this.
I got a question.
What do you do if
someone mugs you here?
If someone mugs me.
Me.
He'll be crying with joy.
He'll think he's in a nightmare.
Good old Andy prepared for that.
Nice pepper spray in
the eyes, eh. Psh, psh, psh.
Bene, bene.
Yeah, then it's just crying
and spitting and whining.
I love you.
I can do that totally discreetly
with a flick of the wrist.
Elegant.
Shhh! As a surprise, right?
Ey cool. Can I have a look?
I love you.
Or this here. This is
for the real tough ones.
80,000 volts.
Ey, Tommie! This one's
got some real juice in it.
Yeah, for a learning effect, right. The
thief should take something with him too.
Hey!
Ha!
Ho!
Sorry, sorry!
That hit the eye, huh.
Yeah, it's okay.
My lady, it's tingling a bit now, huh.
Alma, stay still.
Oh, man. Now just calm down, hey!
But yeah, there's nothing
you can do now, huh. Just wait.
This here, this isn't some water-soup,
huh. I got this from Moscow, huh.
Old KGB stuff, the good old bromo-acetone.
The eyes are running like a hydrant.
You can see it yourself.
Yeah, it really works well, eh.
Si, perfetto.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
- Crazy chicken!
- Aspetta, aspetta.
Hey, where is she going?
Oh, shit!
Madonna.
That was the cactus.
But it's also in a bad spot.
Hearty congratulations.
Cool, that girl. Totally.
Ey, Mario. Step on it. We're
practically standing still.
Wait, there's still more in it.
Wow, ey! Cop, this
is so damn cool, ey.
Always full throttle.
Whoops.
Huhu.
Oh, Tommie, let me too.
Sure, sure.
Tommie!
You idiot!
Ey, watch out,
watch out, watch out!
No!
Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit!
Werner, Werner!
What's going on?
Ah, it was you.
Now, now. You gotta go
outside, something came down.
What's supposed to have come down?
That UFO there.
What? A UFO?
Yeah. It was yellow with loads of flames on
it. Please, please, Werner. Go have a look!
Sure, sure, sure.
Women in menopause.
You stupid potato head.
- Buena sera.
- Hello. Police.
Special operation
by the bike squad.
Is this your vehicle?
Good. This is confiscated.
Where are the keys?
Shit, no more gas.
Tommie, we gotta siphon
some from somewhere.
Ah, look there.
That's good.
What is that?
Ey, party.
Ey, awesome.
Va bene.
Tommie, Tommie. Look at you.
You look like a street cop.
Ey, where are you guys from?
Us? From Cologne.
From the bike squad.
Ah, colleagues from
Cologne. Come over here.
Colleague?
Yeah, just open your eyes, eh.
SEK.
Special Deployment Commando.
Wow.
Ey, then a warm welcome, right.
And where exactly in Cologne
are you guys from, huh?
From Kalk.
Ah, don't get me started. Kalk?
Hey, you there.
Wittmann's over there, right?
Yeah, yeah. Exactly. And the other guy here.
What's his name again? Markus Heinrich.
And Markus and I, we two
are like oil and water. Right?
I think I still got
his number here.
- Hold on, I'll call him right now.
- Why, why?
Nah, no need.
Hello. Schorsch here.
Yeah, I got two of your
buddies right here in front of me.
Yeah. You won't believe it,
it's... what are your names again?
Mario.
Ey, Tommie.
Mario and Tommie, right.
Yeah, you're gonna be
floored now, right.
What?
Oh, the father. That's
the father. No offense.
Markus should
give me a call, right.
Markus Heinrich.
Dad, it's a really bad time.
Who called?
Schorsch. Yeah, yeah.
I'll call him back.
Yes, Dad.
No, I can't talk to Mom
right this second.
Then just tell her...
Hello, Mom.
Yeah, I'm doing good.
Mhm, great.
No, I'm taking
care of myself. Yeah.
Same to you guys. Yeah,
I'll call Schorsch. Thanks.
Guys, I gotta introduce
you to two super-girls, right.
This is Petra and
this is Martina.
- Hey, 'sup!
- Hi.
Come on, let's get to it.
He's so cuddly.
Do you guys want to come along?
Where to?
Hey, you'll see then.
Come on, you tiger.
Drop dead, you piece of filth!
Madonna!
Hello?
What happens then, when
it's finished? If I may ask?
They're hitting on our girls.
This is my fiancée. Right?
And this is my wife.
Thilo, please! We
didn't even want to.
They forced us
and threatened us.
What's wrong with those scumbags?
Threatened?
You shove it right
up their asses.
And this is the
thanks for it. Kalle!
Please, please.
No. Prego.
Go, Kalle. Boom, ba.
Ha, guys, that was a joke.
That's our baptism by fire.
Everyone here has
already been through that.
- Sorry.
- Ey, don't be mad.
- SEK.
- Rüsselsheim!
Once in. Never alone again.
- SEK.
- Rüsselsheim!
Once in. Never alone again.
Rüsselsheim!
Tommie, what were
those girls all about.
Hot, those girls, totally hot.
Awesome.
Do you think... Do you
think, there's still a chance?
Normal. They
stripped specifically for us.
Si.
There, there. There's
the Beckenbauer in him.
The head of the octopus.
Yes, Mr. Beckenbauer.
Yes, Katrin here.
Yes, the event
has already started.
Okay, I understand.
You're stuck in traffic.
- The Beckenbauer...
- This mean Kaiser.
There, there, there, there, there!
Moment please.
What moment? Police!
We are bike patrol.
God bless.
Yeah, normal.
Cheers.
Hey, wait, wait.
Where are you going?
Oops. Scusi, Tommie.
He can burp super well, ey.
Wait, not so fast.
Can't keep up
Man, so fast.
Were you in the tanning salon
for a long time, huh? Looks good.
Hey!
You can go.
Hey, super! Free drinking.
Hey, cool here in Bavaria!
Excuse me please!
Oh, sorry,
sorry.
Hey, hold on.
Hey, wait, wait, wait!
Now please
just stop it.
Well, okay!
Total Wet-T-Shirt, right.
Si!
Tommie!
People are nice here.
Yes, good, good, good. But where
is he now, the, the Beckenbauer?
Yes.
Hello Mr. Knop, may I
disturb you for a moment?
Yes, please. Come on in.
Thanks.
Man, I think it's great, that
you are performing here today.
The ladies and gentlemen sponsors,
they are also really looking forward to it.
You're about to do the imitation
of Mr. Beckenbauer, right?
Right. Yes, exactly. That's
what I'm being paid for.
Then we'll go out onto the field and then
we'll deliver a performance. Yes, exactly.
Man, that's just crazy, how
you do that. Totally real.
My ladies and gentlemen, distinguished
ladies and gentlemen, dear, dear sponsors.
I would now like to most cordially
welcome you to our gala: A Round World.
And although our honorary
president is stuck in traffic...
Look there, ey.
...not let you wait
any longer.
With your help, we were able to acquire the
sponsorship for a small
indigenous village named Ipauiditao.
That's something for the police.
...right in the middle of
the Amazon rainforest.
But we have succeeded in building a soccer
field for the great joy
of the village youth there.
And now, some very high-ranking
guests have come to us from there.
I ask you, please join me in
welcoming Chief Mayo and his son Mia.
- Now, I've got you.
- You're not getting me.
Yamina Mana.
We now have the great honor of being
able to admire the deity Yamina Mana.
At over 3,000 years,
she is the oldest
guardian goddess of the Amazonian
Indians and belongs to the World Heritage.
Right then, potato heads!
Do you know this? And this?
Surrender immediately!
Stop it. I surrender.
Then say you've lost.
You've lost.
Your luck.
So.
Gee, they're practically identical.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Yes, that's the point
of it. Exactly right.
Mr. Knop, a small favor.
It's my dad's birthday today and if you
could just congratulate him really quick.
Like, as Beckenbauer.
That would be really funny.
- Yeah, we'll do that.
- Yes? Oh, great! Thanks. One moment.
- His name is Stefan.
- Stefan. Okay.
Hello?
Yeah, hello Stefan. Yeah, hi there.
- Hello?
- Yeah, it's Franz here, the Beckenbauer.
Hello. Who is that?
Hello.
The Beckenbauer.
- Who?
- The Beckenbauer, Franz.
- Hello. I can't understand you.
- Please, louder.
My dad is
unfortunately hard of hearing.
Hello.
Beckenbauer Franz here.
Yes. Yes, it's me.
Yes, yes. The Kaiser.
Franz Beckenbauer. Yes.
Beckenbauer,
now, we've got you.
And you shall pay for it.
Happy birthday, yes.
Oh, thank you. Franz.
Yes, it's me.
Yes, yes. The Kaiser.
- Yes.
- Beckenbauer!
- Yes, okay!
- Which Beckenbauer?
- Oh thank you very much.
- Yes, you're welcome.
Totally nice. This will be
the hit at home. The Kaiser.
I'll give you Kaiser!
Get down.
Kaiser, you are a criminal!
Wait, wait, wait!
I am not Beckenbauer.
You lying pig.
Kaiser. Where is the goat?
What kind of goat?
Ma, Tommie,
he wants to speak maybe.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. We
can do this another way...
You stole Hennes, ey!
Hello, hello!
Get in there.
Hello.
Mr. Beckenbauer, the delay
I am really very sorry for.
The traffic on the A8,
it's a complete nightmare.
Good evening, Mr. Beckenbauer.
Get in, you mean animal torturer.
You kidnapped Hennes.
No.
Yes you did. I bet you did.
Mario, check if he's got the wart
on his ass. Then we'll have the proof.
Si.
- Let me go!
- Shut up, Kaiser!
And? Do you see anything?
No, there's nothing
there. It's just a lot of hair.
I'm a parodist, after all.
I'm a comedian.
- What are you?
- Imitator!
You should talk like you
always do, Beckenbauer.
Oh, sure, but friends,
hello. I can prove it.
What, what can you prove?
I am not Beckenbauer. I an
impressionist, comedian. Matze Knop.
I am Matthäus, Niki Lauda or
Dieter Bohlen. You might know.
Hello, you are megacool guys in
the green romper outfits here, you.
Shut up. You are not Didi
Bohlen. I know that for sure.
No, but Tommie! That is
also not the Beckenbauer.
Wait, then the
guy totally played us.
That's what I've been
saying the whole time.
What are you thinking,
imitating Beckenbauer.
Si, about the Kaiser
one does not make jokes.
The guy won two World Cups.
That's something like a god.
If you imitate him one more time,
then you'll get a slapping around the ears.
And you'll get 80,000
volts on your naked ass.
Ey, never again in your life will
you say Beckenbauer. Is that clear?
It's clear.
Get lost, get lost.
Tickets for the cup
game Bayern-Hamburg.
Wait a minute.
That's not possible.
- Bayern is playing against Köln in the cup, though.
- Si.
1860 - Köln. Wait a minute.
Mario, we made a mistake.
We aren't even playing
against Bayern, Tommie.
We playing against 1860 Munche.
Oh, man.
Madonna! Porca miseria!
Ah, I see, Mario. Yeah, okay. I'm
just going quickly for a little leak.
Yes, Beckenbauer. Yes.
Tommie, he's already
imitating the Kaiser again.
Now there's
pepper to taste, hey!
Va bene, va bene. Take your pants down,
Tommie. Now he's getting 80,000 volts.
- Stop, I say.
- Shut up, imitator!
Stop, say...
Yeah, what should
we do now, hey.
Maybe we call Addi.
Maybe he is woken up again.
Exactly. Addi. He
knows everything, hey.
Oh, hello Addi.
Si, this is Mario.
No, the Bock, we don't have yet.
We have searched
in Munich like crazy.
Why in Munich?
You did say Munich.
What? You didn't?
Yes, yes.
Hey, Addie, you did
say it exactly. Munich.
Nonsense.
I said we're
playing against Munich.
What?
A guy with the wart on his ass?
Nope, Tommie. I had
the wart on my ass.
What? You had
the wart on your ass?
Yeah,
how am I supposed to express myself
clearly when you're ripping the tubes
out of my throat.
What?
Where I saw the animal
last?
Well, when I put it in the
car.
Well, then the
car was suddenly gone.
When the game against Schalke was.
Ah, let's take the license plates off
and send the cars to the scrapyard.
Ey, exactly, ey. Gone is gone.
Oh, shit. No, nothing.
No, nothing.
I think I know now
where it is. Bye Addi.
Ey, Mario.
We've got the goat.
It's in the box that the
beer driver sawed apart.
Then he is in Cologne
at the scrapyard.
- Tommie!
- Mario!
We found Hennes.
- Normal. We are the best.
- The very best.
- Ey, Super-cop.
- Ey, Supercop.
- Just come to Cologne.
- Va bene.
One-hundred-fifty.
Here we see two
completely normal
police officers who were caught by a
speed camera at a high speed of 155 km/h.
- Yup.
- Quiet there.
- You have to see this.
- But that's your car.
Shortly after, the two had an accident and
flew in a high arc into a manure pile.
The manure pile of the Gröbner family.
Now Gisela believes the two of
them are visitors from another star.
And that the Camaro is a UFO.
Oh, certainly.
I saw it exactly.
That came down from the
sky. Not from the highway.
Oh, and who caught
them with a speed camera?
Well, who says that
you can't flash a UFO.
And why does it
look like a Camaro?
Well, why not. These beings are
way more advanced than we are.
They can replicate
anything, if they want to.
Such stupid babble. Whenever
I hear such stupid babble again.
Anyway.
The two alien police officers now have
enough problems here on Earth as well.
They are, who's surprised,
suspended from duty.
Suspended?
That means they aren't policemen
anymore. Well, wonderful.
You're dead meat.
Tommie, the world is so beautiful.
Exactly. Look, the
beautiful mountains there.
Ma che belle.
Amore and the sunshine.
Tommie!
Why we go to the mountains?
Cologne is not behind the mountains.
Tommie, you idiot.
You potato-head, stop.
Tommie!
You have driven in the wrong
direction.
Yeah, man.
It had been dark, though.
Porca miseria.
What have you done?
Man, we, we...
We can just turn the tractor
around and then drive back.
Macché, turn around?
It's ten past three.
The game starts in two
hours fifty minutes and we...
...we're still in Bavaria!
Ey, totally a disaster, ey!
We fucked up!
Now we're never
going to these girls.
We are the biggest
idiots in the whole city.
Do you think we'll get
another Köln-Kalk ban?
Shut your trap.
Mario, ey, come over here.
That's a Ferrari.
Tommie, this is the rescue.
Yes!
Ey, wait, wait, wait. Police! Stop,
stop. Wait, wait. Wait, moment.
Bicycle squad.
Hello.
Did I maybe
drive too fast?
Then you should punish me.
Okay, I surrender.
Now just grab me
and arrest me.
Oh, shit!
That's shit! Shit!
Signorina, we would love to.
Madonna.
- Yes, but it just doesn't work.
- No.
- Why?
- Because, because, because the goat is in Cologne.
Si.
The goat?
Which goat?
Shit! Such shit! Cut!
Guys, guys,
what happened now?
She was supposed to have a
breakdown and then the mechanic comes.
- Where is he even?
- Here.
Okay. And why did you then...?
Stop it with your
stupid UFO babble.
Werner, these aliens, they're
coming back. Shall we bet?
What do you want to bet? On
your little birdy up here or what?
Werner, they're coming
back. They've chosen us.
If you ask me, they're
already on their way.
Boah, ey, did you see that
chick, ey? Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Madonna, che muamele!
Tommie, that was
Gianna S., right?
No, Spaghetti! Nonsense!
It's not Gianna! That's
the little sister, ey!
Everyone knows that. Janina!
Oh, Tommie, she's so hot!
And her Ferrari, it's
taking off like a rocket, ey.
Kuroma, kumma, 310.
320.
330.
Tommie, Tommie, watch out!
340.
Tommie, no! Tommie,
that's that hill again!
What?
They're coming!
Now you're looking stupid, eh?
We earthlings greet you.
Buon giorno.
Everything all right?
Ey, is he still driving?
The Highway is Hell.
Hey, Mario, there, there!
Hey, 2 hours, 50 minutes.
Is that a cool cut, hey?
Fantastico! Now, Tommie,
nothing more can happen.
Here is the scrapyard.
Si, there it is.
Yes!
Tommie! Hennes.
We made it.
Si.
- Hey!
- Madonna!
Perce dio.
Hey, what's this about?
Help.
Hey, Mario, where are they going?
I don't know, I don't have
a boarding pass with me!
- Shit!
- Willi!
...it's at least another 20
meters, landing on the post.
Hey, Mario, I can see the cathedral.
Oh, you're so stupid, Tommie.
Guys, don't get discouraged
it's all for the sausage!
Hey, Mario, the door is stuck...
...and the wall is
coming, the wall is hitting.
- Oh, shit, shit!
- I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
The beautiful Camaro.
Stop! Help!
...luck for the FC, but now
the follow-up shot. Gooal!
- Shit, boys. Wake up! Fight!
- Zero to one.
Help!
Wait, wait, wait! I got it!
Call him!
- Who?
- Willi.
Si.
Where is the phone?
Moment.
- The phone. In the Ferrari.
- No.
...after three minutes. What a
catastrophic start for the 1. FC.
Where is the phone?
So in the Ferrari, in
the Ferrari, there was...
No, not in the Ferrari,
Tommie. We are in the Camaro.
Get lost! Get lost!
Beautifully crossed in,
immediately five lions rush forward.
No. No!
...Gooal.
Wait. I got the mobile.
Dead silence in the stands. I
don't recognize the fans anymore.
- What is it?
- Willi!
- Whuh?
- Mario, is you that?
- Si!
I can't understand you. At your
end it's so loud. Call again later.
Buzz off.
But not the mobile, Willi.
Zero to three.
The FC is finished.
Willi!
What is it?
Don't turn off the
mobile! The car crusher!
Why? Because we sitting in there.
No, Willi. Is no joke.
Oh, shit!
Oh, Madre Santissima, Mother
of the Gods. You've got me.
Ey, Mario, you know, what
would be cool right now?
What?
If you were a woman.
What? Tommie,
you're a pig!
Go away! Go away!
Yeah, where to?
Jupp!
Come on, let's go back inside.
Ah, I'm not doing that to
myself anymore. Zero to three.
There's no point anymore.
And you, stop with
the pestering.
FC, FC, FC, FC...
Hold on,
who do we have here?
The cops.
Who aren't even cops anymore.
- No. Please, we have to...
- What?
We have to go in there with the truck.
No problem,
I'll take it.
Come along, friends.
Where is my Camaro?
It's in Bocklemund.
And why isn't it here?
Because he didn't drive
properly anymore.
Normal. He was... ow!
He had been in the press
and now he's just such a lump.
What?
But, but, but it makes nothing.
We are rich. Can pay.
- Mhm.
- Oh, yes, sure, sure, sure!
We won the money package, right.
Si. There we exactly
knew and said.
There on TV. That old lady
there, ey, wobbly, wobbly, jiggly.
Si. And then we
both said exactly:
Seagull.
You guys are such
real jokers.
Speaking of the press. Do
you know the Kalk press?
- No.
- Nope.
Then pay close attention.
This here...
these are your nuts.
And this is the press.
And the press presses your nuts.
So my nuts stay intact?
Pants down!
SEK! Rüsselsheim!
Once in, never alone again.
Hu, hu, hu, hu, hu, hu, hu!
Shit, you two!
I'll get you!
I'll rip your asses open!
Hey, listen, hey!
What are you
actually doing here?
We're here because of the Kaiser.
Beckenbauer.
But if you ask me, he's
not all there.
He's gone a bit crazy.
Every time he has to go to the
bathroom, six-man security detail.
And we have to occupy the
other stalls.
Mr. Beckenbauer,
you can come out now.
Well, I can't get out.
Because those are the ones.
I recognize their voices. Do
your homework first, come on.
I told you so, right.
- Thanks.
- Si.
I'll look after you,
Mr. Beckenbauer.
Hello boys.
Hi there.
Guys, guys,
Hennes is back.
I can't believe
my eyes, but it's him!
It's him. Hennes is back!
Allora, allora, make open your eyes!
Goooal!
Goal for our first FC!
Theft of a car under
pretense of official
duty, speeding
by 155 kilometers per hour,
gross misconduct during a
private party in
Munich and sexual harassment
of a dignitary.
I think the game
is over for both of you.
Wait a minute!
I see that quite differently!
Guys?
That thing with
Hennes, that was the
greatest thing anyone
from my team ever did.
And once again:
Goal for our 1. FC.
Ah, you know guys: To be
there in the very last minute...
to be there when it's really important.
Damn it!
That and only that is
the task of our police.
And for that, I'll pull you
out of the biggest pile of shit.
And even if it's the
last thing I do in my life.
But Mr. Wittmann, that is
against the service regulations.
I don't give a shit!
These here are my cops.
My super-cops!
But this time the police
commissioner isn't playing along.
Gentlemen!
Great, absolutely great, boys!
Equalizer!
Three three for our first FC.
Yesss!
That calls for a company
party of the finest kind!
That's not possible! Mr. Police Commissioner,
the last party was only three weeks ago.
FC, FC!
Boys, don't
let yourselves be beaten.
The first corner kick for the FC.
I'm going crazy!
The lead for
our first soccer club.
Shut it.
Tractor sluts,
seven, the second one.
And here we go!
Oh God. My powerful tractor.
Oh God, oh God!
Oh God, the way it shakes me. Oh
man, it definitely has a huge piston.
Oh God, that turns me on.
Hello. May one
perhaps shift into gear?
Yes, yes. Please, put
it in. Ah yes, put it in.
Cut!
Guys, that was great!
Awesome!
Tell me guys, how
did the police
chief actually find you?
We had to
inspect his exhaust.
Exactly, because it
had been loose.
Well. Anyway. The man
really hit the bullseye there.
Cheers!
And one thing I can
assure you.
You two will never be police officers.
Ey, the old lady, she's
got no clue, ey.
Si. This stupid cow.
Ey, they'll get it back.
You didn't do that
for nothing.
No!
Ey, you know what?
For that we're taking
the exhaust with us.
Si, Tommie. At least we ain't
coming home with empty hands.
Exactly.
Ey, this thing's totally sick, right.
And the best part is, there's two
of 'em, man. Everyone gets one.
- Come out.
- One, two, three.
Come out.
Hey! You there.
I don't believe it!
What on earth are you doing there?
What is it?
What am I doing?
Are you not feeling well?
Come. Sit down.
Can I help you in any way,
Mr. Police Commissioner?
Wait, I'll get
you a glass of water, yeah?
Hello.
Hello?
Oh, Mr. President. Yes. Sorry,
I didn't want to disturb you.
But your secretary said
you had a few urgent
personnel recommendations for me.
- Hello?
- Yes.
Uh, do you perhaps already
have the names ready?
- Names?
- Yes, the...
...the names.
Tommie Krause.
Mario Bartolo.
Mhm.
Look there.
Finally normal people!
You aliens,
I'm calling you!
Take me with you to your
planet. I am ready. I am ready.
FC, FC, FC...
FC, FC, F...
Tell me.
Well, blow me.
Who do we have here?
Schalke 04 plays
better than 1. FC Köln.
Played much better. Played wonderful.
Schalke 04 will become champion.
And we are not worthy.
No, not worthy.
We are not worthy.
Not worthy.
...to be at Schalke.
Because we've got no ass on our
flag, there is a solution for everything.
Oh, uh.
No, uh.
Subti  tles: Christopher Coco
(C) 2021 Turbine Medien GmbH
Translateted from German to English
using Ollama and Gemma4